NETFLIX オリジナルシリーズ
SLIDING
So, this is Tanebi Academy!
（シゲオカ）ここが種火(たねび)学園か！
TANEBI ACADEMY
TRANSFER STUDENT - SHIGEOKA
（日花里(ひかり)）ねえ 君
Hey, you!
You're Kakeru, aren't you?
駆(かける)君… だよね？
Dang, you're pretty!
だあっ かわいい！ ああ！
えっ？
なんで？
How do you know my name?
なんで 俺の名前 知ってんの？
The moment he transfers to this school,
a girl flirts with him.
（天の声）
転校早々 まさかの逆ナンパか…
謎の美少女に心奪われたシゲオカ
Shigeoka's heart is captured
by this mysterious young babe.
ところが…
However...
（指を鳴らす音）
（シゲオカ）
ちょっと… なに なに？
やめて やめて！
Hey! What the hell is this?
おい ちょっと待て！
なに なに？ おい！
What the hell is going on?
You're scaring me!
おい 誰だ？ あんた
なあ 怖いって… 怖い！
You're scaring me!
おい！ おい…
Cut it out!
There is a hell of a battle going on
inside the ring.
（実況）
さあ リング上は
いきなり大混戦の模様であります
負けられない戦いが ここにある
They just can't lose this battle.
Wait, what happened to Shigeoka?
だが どうした？ 転校生 シゲオカ
茫然自失
戸惑っております
He's in a daze. He seems lost.
TANEBI ACADEMY FIGHTING RING
その姿は さながら
He looks like a jellyfish caught
in the rough waves of the Japan Sea!
日本海の
荒波にもまれる
ミズクラゲのようで
あります
状況が のみ込めていないのか？
Doesn't he understand what's going on?
Isn't he fired up yet?
まだ熱くなれないのか？
（ナカマ）ぐあっ！
Kotaki doesn't let go of him.
Here goes another throw down.
（実況）
まず フロントからの
キックをお見舞い
コタキが いく
コタキ 強烈！
It's a powerful throw down! And now...
そして… おっと？
-He is on the top rope!
-I'll smash you to pieces.
（コタキ）
ぶっ潰してやるぜ
TRANSFER STUDENT - KOTAKI
ボンタンクラッシュ！
Bontan Crush!
He's flying through the air for...
（実況）
クルクルッと回って なんと！
ロープの高さ
１メートル25センチ
The rope is 1.25m high.
He weighs about 65.3kg.
相手の体重
約65･３キロ
落下速度から割り出せる
衝撃力は…
Expected force of impact
based on the landing speed is...
（実況）
ナカマにキック！
A huge kick to Nakama!
He was blasted out of the ring
飛んでいった
そして リング下に転落！
and landed on the floor!
おっ メガネが…
大事なメガネが なくなっている！
Oh, no! His glasses!
He has lost his precious glasses!
You little...
（キリヤマ）おみゃあ！
（実況）
そして それをアイアンクローで
攻めつけるフジイ！ フジイが…
-Fujii continues with powerful attacks!
-Let go!
-Fujii is...
-Sir!
おぬし…
See if you can take this!
これでも くらっとけ！
It's a tiny sword!
（実況）
ちっちゃい刀だ！
Will he be okay?
Fried Shrimp Chop!
えびふりゃーチョップ！
He attacked him with Fried Shrimp Chop!
（実況）
えびふりゃーチョップが出た！
He moved fast
しかし それを うまく…
（フジイ）
美しいバラには とげがある
-and dodged the attack!
-Beautiful roses have thorns!
Shining Wink!
シャイニング…
ウィンク！
TRANSFER STUDENT - FUJII
Fujii launches his lethal move!
（実況）
フジイの必殺技 炸裂(さくれつ)！
（キリヤマ）どらまぶしいがね！
My god! It's so bright!
ああっ 目が…
My eyes!
うがっ！
Kiriyama has taken a blow!
（実況）
たまらず キリヤマ…
-He's on the floor.
-Are you okay?
（校医）
大丈夫ですか？ 起きてください！
-Wake up!
-The nurse is...
（実況）
保健の先生がビンタの乱れ打ち！
（カミヤマ）もう やだ
I can't take any more of this!
I want to go home!
ウチに帰りたい！
（実況）
カミヤマ 後ろから…
Behind Kiriyama,
（ハマダ）おい やるぞ
-there approaches Hamada!
-Hey, here we go!
What would Hamada do?
（カミヤマ）ひゃあ！
He threw him to the floor.
Would he be able to get up?
うう…
おい…
おい どないなっとんねん？ これ
What the hell is going on here?
（ハマダ）
お前は強いのか？
Are you strong?
TRANSFER STUDENT - HAMADA
What the hell?
（シゲオカ）ハアハア…
（実況）
なんと…
It looks like...
これ 使えよ
-Use this.
-Kotaki...
（実況）
瓶を差し出した
has given him a bottle. Does he want
Shigeoka to bash Hamada with it?
それで殴ろうというのか？
Can Shigeoka do it?
シゲオカ できるのか？
（シゲオカ）う… うわ〜！
-Go!
-Can he really do it?
He's done it!
（実況）
やっちまったぜ〜！
（シゲオカ）うわ〜！
However, Hamada didn't even blink
（実況）
しかし 微動だにしない…
-his eyes.
-Weapons are definitely not allowed.
凶器は いかんよ 凶器は
-I'm sorry.
-Hamada gives him a smile.
（実況）
笑顔まで見せるハマダ
小突いておいて…
He pushes him away...
Hamada Power Muscle!
ハマダパワーマッスル！
（実況）
ハマダの必殺技だ！
It's Hamada's lethal move!
These thoughts ran through his mind,
（天の声）
シゲオカは思った
ちくしょう… 何だ？ こいつら
"Fuck! Who the hell are these guys?
What kind of TV drama is this?"
何なんだ？ このドラマは！
ENTER THE KAKERUS!!
A FEW DAYS EARLIER
（教師）あっ… おめでとう
Congratulations. You're being transferred
to another school.
君の転校が決まったから
転校？
-Transferred?
-Congratulations.
（教師）おめでとう
あ… ん？
What?
You'll be transferred
to the renowned Tanebi Academy.
君の転校先は あの種火学園だ
Tanebi Academy.
種火学園？
どこですか？ それ
Where is that?
（歓声）
（実況）
高〜い所から
ショルダースロー 決まった！
He tossed him very high
with that shoulder throw!
The fight in the ring
has become even more intense!
まさに いよいよ
白熱してまいりました リング上
As you know, Tanebi Academy
ご存じのとおり 我が種火学園は
is where only the very best
high school students
全国の高校から
選ばれし精鋭たちばかりが
across Japan come to compete!
集っている所であります
We hope that the seven competitors
in the ring
本日 我が校にやって来た
リング上の７名にも
give us a fight worthy of the students
of the prestigious Tanebi Academy!
ぜひ 種火学園の生徒にふさわしい
戦いぶりを
見せてもらいたいところです
That's exactly what Transfer Student
Pro Wrestling is all about!
まさに それが
“転校生プロレス”
なのであります！
Transfer Student Pro Wrestling?
転校生プロレス？
ゴホッ ゴホッ…
（コタキ）おら〜！
Hamada and Kotaki trade chops!
Then Fujii gives them his Shining Wink!
（実況）
そして なんと
フジイは いつものように
シャイニングウィンク
シャイニングウィンク！
Shining Wink!
He's done it! This should work!
（実況）
シャイニングウィンク！
しかし それをバリアで…
メンチ切ってんじゃねえぞ こら！
-His lethal move didn't work!
-What are you staring at?
（実況）
なんと
ヤンキーにメンチは禁物だ！
It looks like the delinquent's pompadour
is growing!
伸びていく 伸びていく
It keeps growing!
His hard mousse sure is powerful!
怒りの波動が止まらない！
しかし そのリーゼントを…
He grabbed his pompadour!
-He stopped Kotaki's lethal movement.
-How dare you touch my pompadour?
（コタキ）てめえ よくも…
俺のリーゼントを…
（フジイ）はっ！
Now, Hamada and Fujii grapple!
Hamada lifts him high!
（実況）
さあ ここで
バック取って そして…
高々と持ち上げて！
（フジイ）うっ！ お尻が割れる…
-That looks painful!
-My ass has been ripped apart!
だあ〜！
（実況）
あっ… これは危ないぞ！
Oh, no! This looks dangerous!
なんと！ なんと 拝み渡り！
He's praying on the rope!
是非に及ばず
This is all I can do!
（ハマダ）うわ〜！
（キリヤマ）うっ うっ！ うう…
CRACKING
是非に… 及ばず…
This is all I can take!
（実況）
おっと 転落した！
And he's down!
（キリヤマ）まあかん！
いっ いかんわ これ…
I can't take this!
ハッ… 君 君！
You!
君 あの…
You! Excuse me!
ちょっと あの え〜と
I don't know your name,
so I'm calling you "You"!
名前 分からへんから
“君”って呼ぶけどさ
私の名前？
My name?
日花里よ
I'm Hikari!
It's a combination of characters
from words "sun," "flower,"
日曜日の“日”に
フラワーの“花”
and "origin." It's pronounced Hikari.
お里が知れるの“里”って書いて
日花里って読むの
よろしくね
-Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you, too.
よろしくお願いします
So, Hikari, what the heck is this?
あの〜 日花里ちゃん
一体 これ… 何やろか？
助けてください
-Help me!
-Who are you?
何や お前… 何や？
Sorry. I'm Kamiyama!
すみません カミヤマです
僕 今日
この学校に転校してきたばかりで
-I just transferred to this school today.
-Me, too.
なのに いきなり
リングの上に上げられて
Then I was suddenly thrown into the ring!
You look like the most normal guy here!
君は
いちばん普通の人っぽいから！
普通の人っぽい
-Normal.
-Like you've got it together!
まともそうだし！
まともそうね
I've got it together.
Average! Nothing extraordinary about you!
平凡… とがった部分がない！
Now you're hurting my feelings!
何か傷つくから もう！
（ゴーンという音）
What is that?
（日花里）あれは…
It's finally time to use my power.
ついに この力を使うときが来たか
（実況）
おっと いつの間にやら
Before we knew it,
コーナーポスト最上段に
鎮座ましましている
he has stood himself atop the corner post.
-He's levitating a strange ball of light!
-Oh, my.
謎の光が
うごめいているではありませんか
（キリヤマ）あららら…
This is my secret power!
これが僕の秘められし能力
“ナカマ玉”や
Nakama Globe!
わあ すごい！
Amazing!
あかん… もう状況どころか
世界観にすら ついていかれへん
This is crazy! This situation
just got worse. I'm seeing things!
（カミヤマ）ヒイッ…
写メ 撮ってもええかね？
Can I take a photo?
He's taking a photo!
Who will he send it to?
（実況）
写メを撮っている
どこに送ろうというのか？
ほら お前ら！
Hey, you! If you're scared,
surrender to me!
ビビったんだったら
さっさと降参しろよ
He has challenged them.
（実況）
さあ 挑発してきた
What will happen?
何が起ころうというのか？
おっと 向かっていく！
They jumped up and threw him
to the ground!
そして 投げつける！
My Nakama Globe!
ナカマ玉が…
（実況）
おっと！ 謎の光は
ボールに変わっていって…
What? The mysterious light
has turned into a ball!
え〜？
あそこに なんと 今はやりの
Look! Over there!
It's a projection mapping device!
プロジェクションマッピングが
あるじゃありませんか！
The mystery was just a trick!
謎の手下とグルかよ
え〜 信じられません！
-Unbelievable!
-Hold on a second!
（シゲオカ）
ちょっと ちょっと ちょっと！
（キリヤマ）なにぃ？
What?
（シゲオカ）
お取り込み中のとこ
ちょっと ええかな？
Sorry to bother you while you're busy.
Fine. What is it?
（キリヤマ）う〜ん よかろう
（シゲオカ）
なんで… なんで 俺ら戦ってんの？
Why the heck are we fighting?
What? How the hell should I know?
は？ 知らねえよ
こっちが聞きてえよ
That's what I want to know!
そういえば 俺も よく分からない
Come to think of it,
I don't understand this either.
（キリヤマ）えっ？
What? You're only fighting
because of the excitement?
ほな あちきら
ノリで戦っとったんかね？
You can't do that!
That means suicide for you!
そりゃ いかんでかんわ 御潜伏じゃ
ハハハ！
え？
この人 何か おかしくなってるよ
This guy has lost his mind.
Why do the transfer students
have to fight each other?
どうして 転校生同士で
戦わないといけないんですか？
（キリヤマ）ああ…
Pointless fighting is against the rules
of aesthetics.
無意味な争いは
わたくしの美学に反する
じゃあさ…
All right, then...
The seven transfer students
are staring each other down adamantly!
（実況）
転校生７人 にらみ合ったまま
微動だにしません！
Let's escape this place.
（シゲオカ）こっから逃げようや
（ハマダ）えっ？
What?
The fight inside the ring has gone wild!
（実況）
おお リング下の展開になった！
なんと実況席が…
実況席が壊された〜！
The broadcast table has been crushed!
The audience is in danger!
They're in danger!
蜘蛛の子を散らすように…
観客 危ない！ 危ない 危ない！
危ない状況の中
-The situation has become dangerous!
-Come on!
さあ こんな転校生 見たことないぞ
I've never seen transfer students
fight like this before!
見たことないぞ！ うわ〜！
（観客たちの悲鳴）
（キリヤマ）やあ！
どえりゃ すごいやら！
I've cleared the way!
Thanks! Let's go!
ありがとう！ 行こう！
（キリヤマ:尺八のまね）フウ〜
Doctor, what will happen to Kamiyama?
（フジイ）
先生！
カミヤマ君は どうなるんですか？
-His heart is...
-Yes.
心臓に… あの あの…
Kakeru?
駆君？
（滝沢(たきざわ)）う〜む…
-Let's run away from here!
-Let's go!
Help! Doctor! Please...
If this continues, we will never know.
（日花里）
このままじゃ 何も分からないわ
連れ戻さないと
I have to bring them back.
（警報音）
Emergency!
（校内放送）
緊急事態発生 緊急事態発生
（生徒１）了解した
Understood.
The transfer students
are trying to escape.
転校生たちが逃げたそうだ
You mean those infamous transfer students?
（生徒２:中国語で）
あの噂の転校生か？
（生徒３）
戦い中 逃げ出すとは
とんだヤツらよ
They must be crazy to run away
in the middle of the fight.
（生徒４）
では 捕まえながら
力試しといくかな
Then, let's see how strong they are
while we catch them.
（カミヤマ）
僕も よく知らないんだけど
この種火学園って
I don't really understand it myself,
but you can't get into Tanebi Academy
unless you excel in something.
何か 一芸に秀でてないと
入れないらしいよ
（フジイ）
更に学園内で行われている教育は
全て極秘
What's more, all the classes
this school offers are kept confidential.
This school is an urban legend.
いわば都市伝説のような学校だ
（シゲオカ）
そんな変な学校やったん？
This really is a crazy school.
（カミヤマ）君は？ 何か特技が？
What are you good at?
（シゲオカ）いや 何も
Nothing at all.
進学校で学費がタダってところに
But my mom hurriedly applied
to any school that had free tuition.
うちの おかんが
めっちゃ食いついて
えっ 何か 特技とか あんの？
Are you good at anything?
（カミヤマ）僕も 何も…
I'm not good at anything either.
わたくしも顔が整っているくらいだ
All I have are good looks.
（２人）うん
（足音）
（シゲオカ）お〜！
お〜！
何か楽しそう！
That looks like fun!
You're the transfer students, right?
転校生の人たちだよね？
Come play double Dutch with us!
一緒に跳ぼうよ！
Get down here!
おいで カモン！
That looks really suspicious.
（シゲオカ）めっちゃ怪しいって
Okay! I'll join you!
は〜い！ 僕 跳びま〜す
（シゲオカ）
めっちゃ怪しいって ちょっと…
That looks totally suspicious!
I said that looks suspicious!
怪しいって 絶対さあ…
（笑い声）
Okay!
（生徒）よし！
えっ えっ えっ？
What?
（シゲオカ）うわ〜！
Hey!
ちょっと… えっ？
君 転校生プロレスの
途中だったよね？
You were in the middle of
Transfer Student Pro Wrestling!
You can't just run away!
逃げちゃダメだよ
Get those transfer students, too!
あっちの転校生も捕まえろ！
-How dare you!
-Shit! Let's run!
（シゲオカ）
フジイ フジイ！ 行こう…
Fujii!
（カミヤマ）
置いてかないで〜！
Wait! Don't leave me here! Hey!
Don't leave me!
待って…
FUGITIVE TRANSFER STUDENT
KAMIYAMA CAPTURED
（校内放送）
生徒の皆様に お知らせします
Attention all students!
If you see any
of the seven transfer students
本日 我が種火学園にやって来た
７人の転校生を見かけた生徒は
who transferred to Tanebi Academy today,
発見しだい 速やかに
彼らを生け捕りにしてください
capture them immediately.
転校生プロレスは
大切なイベントです
Transfer Student Pro Wrestling
is an important event.
皆さん
どうか ご協力をお願いします
We appreciate everyone's cooperation.
Any violence or harm caused
to the transfer students will be pardoned.
多少の校内暴力
転校生に危害を加えることが
あってもかまいません
I repeat, capture them immediately!
繰り返します
速やかに
彼らを生け捕りにしてください
（生徒たち）
どこにいる？
どこ どこ？
At present, there is one transfer student
in the south wing,
（校内放送）
現在 南棟付近に１名
図書館付近に
２名の転校生の姿を確認
and another two are near the library.
Please head there immediately!
直ちに そちらに向かってください
繰り返します
I repeat, the seven transfer students
who transferred to this school today...
本日 我が種火学園にやって来た
７人の転校生を
速やかに生け捕りにしてください
Please head there immediately!
繰り返します…
I repeat...
（キリヤマ）
えっ？ 生け捕りって 何？
-Why do they have to capture us?
-I don't know.
（ナカマ）さあ
おい あれ
Hey! Look at that!
（カミヤマ）ん？
（ナカマ）
“ご自由に お使いください”
"Please use these."
（カミヤマ）自由？
Use these?
ほな 着けとこう
Then let's wear them!
Good idea.
（ナカマ）せやな
（キリヤマ）うむ
（キリヤマ）
おめえさん 知っとる？
Did you know
that if you get into this school,
you can go to any school you'd like to go
この学校入ったら
名大 東大 ハーバード
何でも好きな進路に進めるって
話だぎゃ
like Nagoya University, Tokyo University,
or Harvard?
あちきも おぬしも
でら ついてるでござるな
You and I are both pretty darn lucky!
Quit talking. You sound really cheap.
そんなケチくさい話
どうでもええわ
ケチ？
名古屋人はケチじゃにゃあわ！
-Cheap? People from Nagoya are not cheap!
-Keep quiet!
静かにしろって
Listen! The only reason I'm here
ええか？ 僕が知りたいのは
この未知数な学園で
自分の頭脳がどれだけ通用するかや
is to put my wits to the test
at this mysterious school.
はあ〜！ そうですか
Really? Is that so?
戦じゃ 戦！
-This is a battlefield!
-Be quiet!
静かにしろ
Before that...
（キリヤマ）その前に…
let's eat.
栄養じゃ
何や？ それ
What are you talking about?
おい
Here.
半分あげる
-I'll give you half of it.
-Thanks.
ありがとう
いただきます
Thank you for the food.
（ナカマ）うん おいしいな
This is good.
転校生２人を発見！
Two transfer students identified!
-Oh, no!
-They found us!
（キリヤマ）やばい
（ナカマ）いっぱい いた
What should we do?
（キリヤマ）どうしよ…
（ナカマ）ええっ…
（エアガンの発砲音）
（キリヤマ）おっ…
（ナカマ）
おもちゃの銃か おもろい
Those are toy guns.
That's interesting.
（キリヤマ）ほいっ
（キリヤマ）フフフッ…
They're taking it too far!
やり過ぎやろ
（キリヤマ:小声で）おい…
-Let's go.
-Okay.
（ナカマ:小声で）あっ…
（キリヤマ）ハッ…
MANNERISM
ハッ…
コンドルが めりコンドルがや…
The condor got stuck.
FUGITIVE TRANSFER STUDENTS
KIRIYAMA AND NAKAMA CAPTURED
生け捕りで…
Capture us...
お願いしま〜す
please.
So, now it's just you,
次は てめえか
仏頂面！
the tough guy!
どうやら そのようだな
So it seems.
Let's do this.
いくぞ
なんで… 結局 戦うのかよ
Why?
You are going to fight anyway!
どうせ戦うならリングで…
If you're going to fight,
do it in the ring!
ここじゃなくて
リングの上でしてくれよ
Don't do it here! Go fight in the ring!
Yes! Don't waste your punches on us!
っていうか俺たち 殴られ損だろ
FUGITIVE TRANSFER STUDENTS
HAMADA AND KOTAKI CAPTURED
何や？ あいつら 気持ち悪い！
-Who are those creepy people?
-Butterfly!
（水泳部員たち）
バタフライ バタフライ…
-Butterfly!
バタフライ バタフライ
バタフライ バタフライ…
-Butterfly!
-They're creeping me out!
（シゲオカ）気持ち悪い！
-Butterfly!
-So beautiful!
-Fujii?
（フジイ）美しい…
（シゲオカ）フジイ？
（フジイ）行ってくれ！
-Run! I will remain here
-Butterfly!
わたくしは ここで美しく散る
-and die a beautiful death
-Butterfly!
-like Icarus!
イカロスのように！
-Icarus? What?
-Butterfly!
イカロス？ は？
（フジイ）
さあ わたくしを捕まえにきて！
-Come and get me!
-Butterfly!
（水泳部員たち）
バタフライ バタフライ…
-Butterfly!
（シゲオカ）え？
-Why do you look so happy?
-Butterfly!
なんで幸せそうなん？
お前
-Okay, I'm leaving!
-Butterfly!
なあ…
おい 行くぞ 俺 先！
FUGITIVE TRANSFER STUDENT
FUJII CAPTURED
（フジイ）おお おお…
イエス イエス！
-Yes!
-Butterfly!
了解
Understood.
So, there's only one left.
じゃあ あと１人ね
-Find them!
-Where are they?
（女子生徒）どこや〜！
（生徒たち）どこだ どこだ！
こっち
Come in here.
-Check this way!
-Over here!
（生徒たち）
あいつは どこだ？
どこ行った？ 捜せ〜！
-Where is he?
-Check over there!
（生徒たちの騒ぎ声）
日花里ちゃん ありがとう
Thank you, Hikari.
あの ホント…
日花里ちゃんが助けてくれるなんて
You are the one who rescued me, Hikari...
俺 運命 感じる
I think we are destined.
I mean...
こう…
俺 初めて日花里ちゃんに
会ったときから こう…
the first time I met you, Hikari,
it felt like my heart
was shouting out, "Hallelujah!"
胸の中で…
ハーレルヤの気持ちが
すっごい湧いてきて！
SLAPPING
Ouch!
（シゲオカ）痛っ…
It hurts!
痛い…
-You're a coward!
-What?
意気地なし！
How dare you run away from a fight?
You scaredy-cat, fraidy-cat, pussycat!
目の前の戦いから逃げるなんて
芋虫 毛虫 ダンゴ虫よ！
もう ガッカリだわ
What a disappointment!
I don't understand what's going on,
but I'm sorry.
何か分からへんけど すいません
こんなじゃ
ミッションにも耐えられない
You'll never make it through any missions.
Missions?
（シゲオカ）ミッション？
な… 何なの？ 一体 この学校
What kind of place is this school?
I'll tell you later what this school
is really about!
それは あとで話す！
この学園の本当の姿
でも 今は
転校生プロレスのリングに戻って
Right now, Kakeru, you need to get back
in the ring and fight
in Transfer Student Pro Wrestling!
駆君 戦うのよ！
But I have no reason to fight!
いや 俺 だって
戦う理由がないんやもん
If you win...
もし勝ったら…
you can do anything you want to me.
私を めちゃくちゃにしてもいい
What did you say?
何やて？
駆君
Kakeru...
私が欲しかったら戦って
if you want me, then fight.
（シゲオカ）あ〜！
Oh, yes! Oh, my god!
ちょっと〜！ ちょっと…
不純な思いはさ 一切…
一切ない 不純な思いは！
I'm not thinking of doing anything naughty
with you at all,
だけど がっ… 俄然(がぜん)
やる気が湧いてきた〜！
but I'm suddenly all fired up!
I swear I'll win!
絶対 勝つ！ 絶対 勝つぞ！
よし！ 絶対 勝つぞ
日花里ちゃ〜ん！
I swear I'll win, Hikari!
ああ…
If I win...
（シゲオカ）勝てば…
I can... with Hikari...
日花里ちゃん
ああ 日花里ちゃんと…
ハア〜
（ナカマ）何？ 鼻息 荒いな
What? Why are you breathing so heavily?
（ハマダ）
やはり 戦うしかないみたいだな
It seems we have no choice but to fight.
（キリヤマ）
こりゃ ひとつ やるしかにゃあがや
It looks like we'll just have to do this!
ハハハハ…
（フジイ）ん？
（日花里）
元気ですか！
Are you ready?
駆君
Kakeru.
日花里ちゃん
Hikari.
（日花里）
この勝負で あなたが
絶対に勝てる方法を教えてあげる
I'll teach you how to win
this fight for sure.
駆君
Kakeru,
あなたにしかできない
必殺技があるの
you have a lethal move
that only you can do.
俺にしかできない必殺技？
A lethal move that only I can do?
ごめん　はい
Sorry. Here.
（日花里）
そう それは“国電(こくでん)パンチ”
Yes.
It's called National Railway Punch.
国電パンチ？
National Railway Punch.
そんなふうに言われると
When you say that,
その気になって
右腕がブルブルしてくるでしょ？
you can feel your arm
starting to tremble, right?
してくるはず！
It should!
してきた！
It's starting!
右腕 ブルブルしてきた！
My right arm is trembling!
（日花里）
さあ 駆君！
Okay, Kakeru, it's time to release
that legendary lethal move!
今こそ
その伝説の必殺技を放つのよ！
駆君ならできる！
You can do it, Kakeru!
勝って 勝って 勝ちまくって
You'll win, and you'll keep on winning!
輝く未来を手に入れるのよ！
You'll have a brilliant future!
A brilliant future!
輝く… 未来！
Kakeru!
（日花里）
駆君！
うお〜！
National Railway Punch!
国電パ〜ンチ！
Something is shooting out!
何か出てる〜！
ぎゃ〜！
（天の声）
国電パンチとは
National Railway Punch
has the destructive power
of the National Railway!
国電の持つ破壊力を備えた
パンチなんだが
詳しくは 原作「炎の転校生」
文庫版２巻をご覧いただこう
For details, see volume two
of the pocket edition
of Blazing Transfer Student.
This legendary lethal move
この伝説の必殺技を
７人の転校生が放った！
is being unleashed
by the seven transfer students!
Hold on! By the seven of us?
（シゲオカ）
ちょ ちょ ちょっと… ７人？
（キリヤマ）ああ…
（ハマダ）うおっ うおっ！
（コタキ）うっ…
（フジイ）う〜！
（カミヤマ）あっ あっ…
（ナカマ）ウソや〜！
It's hot!
（７人）国電パ〜ンチ！
-National Railway Punch!
はあ？
What is going on?
どういうこと？
美しい衝撃だ
It was such a beautiful impact.
つうか…
But...
国電って何だよ？
what does "National Railway" mean?
（天の声）
ちなみに 国電とは
By the way,
いわゆる
１つの日本国有鉄道の電車のことで
the National Railway
was one of the railways the country ran
before JR was introduced.
ＪＲが誕生する前の
大都市圏の足であったわけよ 足！
It was how people
got around the cities and suburbs!
なるほど…
I see.
On the first day after transferring
to the mysterious school, Tanebi Academy,
（天の声）
転校初日 謎の学校 種火学園に
やってまいった７人の
一体から八体から
わけが分からねえ戦いは
the seven students
ended the baffling fight in a draw
わけが分からねえ必殺技によって
by using a baffling lethal move.
引き分けで幕を閉じた
It looks like we'll have
to settle this later,
勝負は お預けみたいね
駆君…
all of you...
“たち”
Kakerus.
（滝沢）
国電パンチの使い手が７人も…
All seven of them
can use National Railway Punch.
これは
ますます分からなくなったな
This has become an even greater mystery.
（日花里）校長
Principal.
本日
我が種火学園に転校してきた—
These are the students that transferred
to Tanebi Academy today.
Kakeru Shigeoka.
シゲオカ駆君
Kakeru Kotaki.
コタキ駆君
Kakeru Nakama.
ナカマ駆君
Kakeru Kiriyama.
キリヤマ駆君
Kakeru Fujii.
フジイ駆君
Kakeru Kamiyama.
カミヤマ駆君
Kakeru Hamada.
ハマダ駆君
以上 ７人の駆君たちです
They are all the seven Kakerus.
（シゲオカ）全員 駆やったん？
We're all named Kakeru?
（ナカマ）
統計学的に ありえへん偶然やな
This is a statistically impossible
coincidence.
（キリヤマ）アッハハ…
（滝沢）ようこそ 種火学園へ
Welcome to Tanebi Academy!
（フジイ）マネキン？
（カミヤマ）えっ？
-A mannequin?
-It's a doll!
（キリヤマ）うわっ 人形だぎゃ！
（日花里）いいえ！ 校長です
No! He's Principal!
（滝沢）そう！ 私は校長の滝沢昇(のぼる)
That's right!
I am the principal, Noboru Takizawa.
君たちの戦いぶりは
見せてもらったよ
I watched you fight.
君たちを この学園の一員として
歓迎しよう
I welcome you as members of this school!
もう分かってると思うけど
I think you can tell that Tanebi Academy
is not an average school.
この種火学園は普通の学校じゃない
（滝沢）そう
Right!
This school is actually
この学園の実態は
“炎の転校生”養成所だ
the training ground
for Blazing Transfer Students.
養成所？
Training ground?
何ですか？
その“炎の転校生”って
What is Blazing Transfer Student?
（滝沢）
かつて
私が使っていたコードネームだ
It's the code name
that I used in the past.
NATIONAL RAILWAY PUNCH!
ヤツの行く所
嵐 飛び交い 稲妻 走る
Wherever they go,
they bring storms and lightning!
BLAZING TRANSFER STUDENT
懐かしい話だ
It's a good old story.
今は この学園の生徒たちに
そのミッションを託している
Now, the students here
are assigned to missions.
そのミッションとは
Their mission is to transfer
to problematic schools across the country,
全国の問題のある学校に転校
生徒として潜入し
学校内部から改革を行うこと
infiltrate them as students,
and reform them from the inside.
（滝沢）今日から君たち７人は
From today, you seven will
be transfer-student agents,
転校生型エージェント
“炎の転校生”となるのだ！
Blazing Transfer Students!
これから君たちは
From now on,
さまざまな学校の問題に
直面するだろう
you'll be coming face-to-face
with a variety of school problems.
しかし その全てをやり終えたとき
However, as you complete
all missions assigned to you,
君たちには
すばらしい未来が待っているのだ
there is a glorious future awaiting you!
（７人）すばらしい未来？
-A glorious future?
はい！
Yes!
I will be a Blazing Transfer Student!
俺 炎の転校生 やります！
（ハマダ）俺も やるぞ！
-I will, too!
-I'll do it, too!
（駆たち）
俺も！
やります！
よろしく
-Good. Nice to meet you.
-Thank you.
（キリヤマ）おお よろしくね！
Thank you.
（フジイ）よろしく
BASED ON THE COMIC SERIES
BLAZING TRANSFER STUDENT
（キリヤマ）
俺も よろしくね
Thank you.
（天の声）
こうして 校長 滝沢の
漠然とした言葉につられ
With these vague words
from Principal Takizawa,
新たに７人の
炎の転校生が誕生した
seven new Blazing Transfer Students
were born!
〜
Subtitle translation by Brian Athey